Guide to the Time Inc. Staff Organizations 1940-2015 MS 3009-RG 18
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Time-Life Alumni Society (TLAS) Collection, 1940-2015; 6 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
  - Subseries III.D. Audiovisual materials [RESTRICTED], 1985-2001; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    - Miscellaneous: Crane, Ralph; Grant, Allan; Parks, Gordon, undated (Offsite-box 2790, Item 19)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "The LIFE Photographers: Allan Grant (3 short films); Gordon Parks Personal Bio; Ralph Crane's Memorial with LIFE photographers: Peter Stackpole, Loomis Dean, John Florea and John Zimmerman".
    - Miscellaneous: Unlabeled tape, undated (Offsite-box 2790, Item 20)
      1 videocassette (VHS). No identifying label.
  - Subseries III.E. General, 1986-1999; 0.1 Linear feet in 3 folders
    Contains newspaper clippings, obituaries, photographs, magazine drafts, and correspondence.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - "Life @ 50" Prints, 1986 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings, Obituaries, and Photographs from Jim Pitt, 1992-1999 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 12)
    - Superbash, 1988 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 13)